Every moment people that's coming in now. We got dubs wubs with a hot chip challenge for 2023
Set by Brandon Mitchews. Um, thank you Brandon Mitchews very much. Dub wubs is gonna open here live
There we go, look at this fresh
Don't squeeze it too much. I'm gonna tell you guys something about devs though. When he was here homie eats jalapenos like their carrots like
I'm posting you at that point of eating hot stuff, so
You doing the one chip challenge with double ups
I don't want the camera yet.
Oh, no, I dropped it.
Um, I'm good.
Oh, tops.
I have a look at the comments.
Is there a bunch of people in here now?
We still wait.
We got 28 people right now waiting for you to open the chip
and right now, because in like 30 seconds
to a minute, the bubble's going to look at the list.
See how long he got to last.
And then he's going to start the challenge
and like one minute from now.
So pull out the paper that comes with it and show everybody.
Welcome here. It is welcome. What is right there? These are the rules people show it on the screen you on big screen, so all right right there stop
somebody read that
Read the warning good. Oh you check it down read the warning eat the chip eat the entire chip
Wait as long as possible for drinking or eating anything post your reaction on social media with
Hashtag one trip challenge and mentioned
Okay, the clock the clock
Needless for clock name the box. Yeah name the box the challenge you did. All right. What's the paper? Oh, you gonna become the slayer
What the paper says the paper says what?
Okay
One minute ten minutes thirty minutes lift it up lift it up
Little up little up
There you go right there one hour
All right, let's see if he can let out these are the time limits
So depending on what dubs complete without touching water for one minute ten minutes or 30 minutes to an hour
We see how much of a champion he is. Let's go dubs. Start it up
Hold on let me put the sound of that
Me and Easy know what it's like.
He like really said it.
He got it.
It isn't as bad as you think it is.
It's done.
This is a solid challenge.
This is solid.
It's solid.
It's not broken.
But I'm allowed to uh...
Do whatever I wanted the chip, right
Well when I did it I put the whole thing and it made my mouth mad dry
So I don't know if you want to just put it in little crumbs and then just like chew on it
I don't know that's up to you
I would break it like in half, maybe so it doesn't touch the teeth.
I'm ready, I'm just about to be a baby, let's go, I'm ready, I'm going to drink for you.
Hey, you guys got a glove?
Because once I touch this, I can't touch anything, it's going to burn.
Do you want me to take it out of your bag?
Listen, dubs, don't take it out the bag, just pour it right into your mouth.
It doesn't matter what you think. I mean, I just not gonna touch the actual chip. So that's the key
Right now 51 people saying eat the chip hole
I already broke it. I don't care. I don't I'm gonna eat the whole damn thing just all at once, but I
Can't rightfully touch it and then like touch
You don't need no gloves. They say do it like a man. Yes
You're out of your fucking mind. I'm I want some gloves. You're out of your fucking mind
Touch a pee pee after
I went to watch it all off, and I watched all that right down my whole body. I was like, ah, why does my dick hurt?
Oh, yeah, I was amazed
It's going down people the bag is just open
Let's go to Louis B used to me, you know, he's gonna burn his ass dubs you can't get off that shit
You gotta stay in view you gotta stay in view
Well, I know that's I mean I got everything's all comfortable. Yeah. Yeah, you get up make sure you take the camera with you. I
Can smell it smell it dog smell it smell it smell it. They say
It smells terrible
It's going down this stuff's got it. Oh look at it. Look. Oh my god. That's not even
Burgundy
Oh my god, Hulk fan. What up my guy?
No, no, no, no, no, no, don't keep your hand in sight. Keep your hand in sight. Your hand got to stay in sight, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them, let them,
Seven six five four three those who know
Good thing. I don't speak Spanish now do that shit again
Three two one nigga get going
Bitch put it in your mouth. What's up?
I'm counting right now is that 12 minutes? He started like that's what I try to get at 12 is that but
Little bit after since 12 minutes
All right after you swallow right I got a question for you and we're gonna have questions from the chat coming up too from your
Peoples and everybody else's all right. How do you feel?
It's gonna kick in in like five three to five minutes
Well, no water. No ice cream. No beer. No none of that for one whole hour. You are the champ
By 12 fuck here we go
Now you can start wiping your face. Oh, I already know you swearing you look the red is coming up people
I mean, you know what it feels like to me.
Come on now.
This is just something like I'm cheering up.
That's the thing.
I remember this feeling right now.
I'm sweating.
I'm watching him eat this.
I'm wiping my face right now, people.
Oh, my God.
But look on his face.
Just make the way I feel when they give me Narcan.
All right.
Let's go with the people on panel.
We've got some questions for Doves right now.
Doves, you've got to answer these questions while you suffer.
I don't know. He's like I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.
Do I
He's already done better than Brooklyn audit
All right, all right, let's see what the chat say. Oh shit, I missed a lot. I was in the other